

# ALLEN HE

CONTACT PORTFOLIO

3083 Parkway Cir, El Monte, CA 91791

t: 626 863 9208 | e: heswebs@gmail.com | w: heswebs.github.io/portfolio/

linkedin.com/in/hehongde in

### **OBJECTIVE**

Web Developer with 5 years of front-end experience looking for opportunity to utilizing my abilities. Bringing mockups to life using HTML, CSS, JavaScript. Creating and optimizing user friendly, responsive, high-speed and search engine friendly web applications.

#### EXPERIENCE

AEE Technology Inc. Front End Developer 2016 - Present

OODDA INC. Web Developer 2015 - 2016

iBUYPOWER INC. Web Developer 2013 - 2015 - Building company responsive Websites.

- Creating HTML email templates and newsletters for e-mail marketing campaigns.
- Implementing a mobile-first approach to existing websites
- Maintaining and optimizing the existing websites to ensure its availability, accessibility, speed, search engine visibility and e-commerce security
- Translated design team's wireframes and mockups into responsive websites, using HTML/CSS and JavaScript
- Worked with clients from varied fields to plan and develop web and web features.
- Executed and contributed to full-stack web development projects, with an emphasis on front end features, browser manipulation, and cross-browser compatibility.
- Enriched and Maintained company website (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Translated design team's PSD wireframes and mockups into responsive websites, using HTML/CSS and JavaScript
- Creating responsive simple page templates using modern CSS techniques and JavaScript

# **EXPERTISE**

HTML5	
CSS3	
JavaScript	
Bootstrap	
ReactJS	
LAMP	
SASS	
FlexBox	
CSS Grid	

SEO Responsive Web Web Accessibility Web Troubleshooting

## EDUCATION

California State Polytechnic University, Pomona, California 2011 - 2013

**Bachelor in Computer Information Systems degree**